export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "10/2+1",
        options: [6,2,3,9],
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "2*8/2",
        options: [5,2,8,1],
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "6+2-8",
        options: [0,5,2,1],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "1-2-1",
        options: [2,-5,-2,-1],
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "89*3/3",
        options: [89,45,32,27],
        answer: 89
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "9*1/1",
        options: [9,1,0,2],
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "4/4",
        options: [1,0,4,2],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "9*1/2",
        options: [4,0,1,2],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "3-1-2",
        options: [1,8,9,0],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "0+2+1",
        options: [0,1,3,2],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "0+0+1",
        options: [2,1,3,0],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "5-6-1",
        options: [-1,-2,-3,-4],
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "0/9",
        options: [9,0,1,2],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "7/1+1",
        options: [8,0,1,7],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "9*1/1",
        options: [9,1,0,2],
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "6+2-8",
        options: [0,5,2,1],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "1-2-1",
        options: [2,-5,-2,-1],
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "1-2-1",
        options: [2,-5,-2,-1],
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "89*3/3",
        options: [89,45,32,27],
        answer: 89
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "7/1+1",
        options: [8,0,1,7],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "9*1/1",
        options: [9,1,0,2],
        answer: 9
    },

]